[ Research Activity](https://anthrotech.optimalworkshop.com/optimalsort/snohomishcountycardsort) [We are doing research to improve our website and would like your input! Please take 15 min to participate, with a chance to win 1 of 5 $50 gift cards. Start the online activity now!](https://anthrotech.optimalworkshop.com/treejack/snocott)

 [](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/Search/Results) Search

### 

1. [Home](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/)
2. [My Account](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/MyAccount)
3. [Printer Friendly](#PrinterFriendly4879ede2-61ae-4f4f-bbef-658a2bee32f1)
4. [Email Page](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/EmailPage)
5. [Contact Us](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/directory.aspx)
6. [RSS](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/rss.aspx)
7. [Site Map](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/SiteMap)
8. [Translate Page](#TranslatePage4879ede2-61ae-4f4f-bbef-658a2bee32f1)
9. [Notifications](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/list.aspx)
10. [Documents](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/DocumentCenter)

1. [County Services](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/31/County-Services)
2. [Your Government](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/127/Your-Government)
3. [Doing Business](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/35/Doing-Business)
4. [Our Community](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/9/Our-Community)

1. [CustomLinks\_35](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/2760/CustomLinks-35)
2. [Site Tools](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/2120/Site-Tools)
3. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Personal Information
--------------------

All information collected at this site becomes a public record that may be subject to inspection and copying by the public unless an exemption in law exists. For further details, see the Revised Code of Washington (RCW) 42.56.040. Public information exemptions are detailed in the RCW 42.56.210. Public information includes correspondence with the county such as emails, website comments, and feedback.

Snohomish County may use "cookies" to store information that can be reused during subsequent visits to the Snohomish County website. A website cookie is a small text file that a web server stores on a user’s computer. This information usually is limited to a generated user ID or site presentation preferences. Web browsers can be configured to reject the storage of "cookies" on the user's PC if desired.

Snohomish County is subject to state and federal laws assuring the public's right to access public records and information. Public information involves information about activity that is regulated. For example, the purchase of legal documents provides public information and is regulated by state and county laws and code. If such a purchase was by credit card, the credit card information is not public information and would only be shared to those trusted entities required for processing (for example third party credit card verification services).

Linkage
-------

Snohomish County links to external websites as a service to provide additional information and reference material that may be helpful on county-related subjects. Such links are not an endorsement in any form by Snohomish County. Snohomish County is not responsible for the content of those linked sites. Snohomish County policy limits the use of links to public sites in most cases. Links to commercial sites are only appropriate when a reasonable comprehensive representation of a service via a link or series of links can be accommodated. In such cases, these links are only provided in the hope that users find reference material on county-related subjects.

Snohomish County will always attempt to assure that the information presented on its website is accurate and timely. However, neither Snohomish County, nor any agency, officer, or employee of Snohomish County warrants the accuracy, the reliability, or timeliness of any information published by this system, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from this system, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability, or timeliness of such information. Any person or entity that does rely on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.

Security
--------

Snohomish County web servers contain security precautions that prevent personal information from being stolen or tampered with. Personal financial information that is exempt from public disclosure under Chapter 42.56 RCW will be protected. Financial information will be protected by secure sockets layer (SSL) software, which encrypts all information before being securely sent across the Internet. Additional security measures that Snohomish County Department of Information Services deems appropriate may be employed as well.

Please direct your comments about this statement to the [website coordinator via email](mailto:websitecoordinator@snoco.org).

[County Records  
Request Public Records](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/1704)

[County Jobs  
Current opportunities](https://www.governmentjobs.com/careers/snohomish)

[Jury Duty  
Keep Informed](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/5519)

[Payments  
Easily pay your bills online](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/3111)

[Waste  
What you need to know](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/207)

[Taxes  
Search our database](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/2251)

[Licenses  
Application information](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/1609)

1. [Accessibility](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/accessibility)

1. [Copyright](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/site/copyright)

1. [Privacy Policy](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/privacy)

1. [Site Information](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/1965/Website-Information)

1. [Webpage Feedback](https://snohomishcountywa.gov/howarewedoing)

1. [Translate](http://translate.google.com/translate?js=n&sl=auto&tl=es&u=https://www.snohomishcountywa.gov/#TranslatePage2dddd745-2c39-4d70-a17f-88384b2ae058)

/QuickLinks.aspx

1. Snohomish County Government     3000 Rockefeller Avenue     Everett, WA 98201     Phone: [425-388-3411](tel: 425-388-3411)

1.  Government Websites by [CivicPlus®](http://www.civicplus.com/)  

### Loading

Loading

Do Not Show Again Close

Arrow Left Arrow Right

\[\]

Slideshow Left Arrow Slideshow Right Arrow
